(Penny:)Trust me,
this is the right thing.
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Leonard:)And it's not like
we're abandoning him.
(Leonard:)Plus,
(Leonard:)we can FaceTime him
whenever we want,
(Leonard:)you know, once iPhones
are invented in his universe.
(Bernadette:)I can't believe Sheldon
(Bernadette:)asked you to be his roommate.
(Bernadette:)I can't believe
he ran my credit.
(Bernadette:)Hey, if you're open to living
with someone great,
I'll give you $1,000
to take Stuart.
(Amy:)You really should've gone
on the Internet
(Amy:)and checked how long
that kind of thing lives
(Amy:)before you got one.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
(Bernadette:)I just thought you might have
(Bernadette:)a pasty, weirdo-shaped hole
in your life.
(Amy:)Hey, I know Sheldon's quirky,
(Amy:)but he's also brilliant
and insightful.
(Amy:)I think calling him a weirdo
is a little unfair.
Hello, 2003!
(Leonard:)Hey, we brought you Thai.